http://middlesexrugby.com/privacypolicy/

Middlesex Rugby Privacy Policy
This statement discloses the privacy policy for www.middlesexrugby.com the official website of the Middlesex Rugby (the operating name for Middlesex County Rugby Football Union Limited).
Middlesex Rugby is committed to protecting and respecting your privacy and ensuring a secure online experience. In general, you can view this site and all the latest news and results without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself.
Collection of Personal Information
Middlesex Rugby offers certain functions and services which, if you choose to use them, will require information from you in order to work, such as your name, email, address and telephone number.  Middlesex Rugby will endeavour to let you know before your personal information is collected from you on the Internet.
Use of Personal Information
Where we do collect your personal data we use it primarily for the following purposes:
To perform the services you have requested
To make the site easier for you to use by not making you enter your personal information more than once
To help you find what you’re looking for quickly
To help us create and deliver content most relevant to you
Middlesex Rugby may use the personal data you provided for membership purposes and the administration of the game, but will seek your consent before doing so.
Middlesex Rugby will not use (or pass to any third party) contact data on children under the age of 13.
Processing Your Data
If you choose to give us personal information to process an order or provide you with a subscription to a free service then this will be held and processed by Middlesex Rugby in accordance with the General Data Protection Regulation 2018 and the Data Protection Act 1998.  We will not pass your data to third parties with the following exceptions: Middlesex Rugby may also need to transfer your personal information to the RFU for administration of the game.  Personal data may be shared with government authorities and/or law enforcement officials if required by law or if required for the legal protection of our or the RFU’s legitimate interests in compliance with applicable laws.
Providing you with information
Middlesex Rugby may use your personal information (where you have supplied it) to supply you with information about Middlesex Rugby and/or its related organisations, and new services offered to the game, as well as their respective activities and ranges of goods, services and opportunities (and otherwise where you have given your consent).
We also keep track of the domains from which users visit and analyse this data:
For trends and statistics and to evaluate the efficiency of our web site and our internet infrastructure
To ensure that services offered (such as, but not limited to, chat and forums) are not abused
We may also use your information for detection of fraud.
Business relationships
The Middlesex Rugby website contains links to other websites.  Middlesex Rugby is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of external websites.
Cookies
Information may be sent to your computer in the form of an Internet “cookie” to allow Middlesex Rugby servers to monitor your requirements. The cookie is stored on your computer. The Middlesex Rugby server may request that your computer return a cookie to it.
These return cookies do not contain any information supplied by you or any personally identifiable information about you.
Such measures are necessary to allow Middlesex Rugby to measure the usability of the systems, which will help to continually improve user experience of our websites.
Your browser software should however enable you to block cookies if you wish to. For more information about cookies, please visit www.allaboutcookies.org
Consent
By submitting your personal information to us to request a service, we will make clear that we are seeking your consent for us to use the information to provide the service requested.  If we amend our privacy policy, any changes will be published on this web site.  If at any time you wish to update the information which we hold about you, or if you wish to stop receiving information from Middlesex Rugby, please contact us (click here).
What rights do I have?
You have the right to ask us for a copy of your personal data we may hold about you; to correct, delete or restrict (stop any active) processing of your personal data; and to obtain the personal data you provide to us for a contract or with your consent in a structured, machine readable format.
In addition, you can object to the processing of your personal data in some circumstances (in particular, where we don’t have to process the data to meet a contractual or other legal requirement).
These rights may be limited, for example if fulfilling your request would reveal personal data about another person, or if you ask us to delete information which we are required by law to keep or have compelling legitimate interests in keeping.
Copyright © 2020 Middlesex County Rugby Football Union. All Rights Reserved.
Middlesex RugbyPK1 Twyford Avenue Sports GroundTwyford AvenueActon, London W3 9QA+44 (0)20 8896 9050moc/ybgurxeselddim//eciffoytnuoc
Home
Policies
Constituent Body
Privacy Notice
Sitemap
Contact us
Middlesex Rugby is the official RFU constituent body for Middlesex. It's role is to grow and develop rugby union and its member clubs within the county, and promote the core values of the game.
X
Home
Covid-19
County
Committees
President’s Corner
Governance
Safeguarding
